Lewis Farut Noguera Gómez

UI Designer and FullStack Javascript Developer | React-Native Developer

Email: Lewisnoguera@gmail.com

Tel: (+57) 320 797 1953

Github: https://github.com/LewisFNoguera
Portfolio: https://lewisnoguera.netlify.app

| About me

I am a FullStack developer and graphic designer focused on UI, with more than 6 years of experience in UI implementation, as well as interactivity and functionality. I have skills in web development using HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript and different frameworks and libraries like Angular, ReactJS, or VueJs. In the backend, I use Node, Express and NestJS and implement user interfaces for mobile applications using frameworks like SenchaTouch and ReactNative. In addition, I have worked as a UI designer, creating prototypes and wireframes in Figma and AdobeXD. I'm enthusiastic and passionate about new technologies and I'm always open to learn new things.

| Experience

Monetta

Position: Frontend Developer | React-Native Developer

October 2021 - At Present

Design and development of reusable modules and components for the main app in React-Native; design and development of modules and components for the product's admin CMS using React and TailwindCSS; design and development of static web pages with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript; design of components in Figma; and creation of REST backend services with NestJS and Node.

Cetoco

Position: Frontend Developer | React-Native Developer | UI Designer October 2020 - October 2021

I designed user interfaces for the Monetta app and client companies like OWO, and Banco Davivienda (Maps) in **Figma** and **AdobeXD** and I developed those features in code. I worked as Front-end developer through libraries or frameworks such as **React-Native**, **React**, **Angular**, and **TailwindCSS** for administrative **CMS** and websites. Implementation of agile methodologies such as **SCRUM** and use of tools such as **BITBUCKET** and **JIRA** for development team management and goal achievement.



Adatec

Position: UI Designer | Frontend Developer

August 2015 - September 2020

Design of graphical user interfaces for cell phones and websites, UI implementation in React and Sencha Touch. Design and development of business websites, such as product pages and homepages, based on WordPress. Generation of graphic pieces for social networks, design and development of pieces for Mailchimp. Modification and use of ticketing tools, such as OSTicket.

| Skills

Operating systems: MacOS

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript

Frameworks / Libs: React, Vue, Angular, Astro, React Native, Node, Express

CSS: Sass, TailwindCss, TailwindUI

Design: Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Adobe Acrobat

Tools: SCRUM, Postman, GitHub, Styled Component.

| Education

The Corporación Universitaria Minuto de Dios (UNIMINUTO) | Colombia (2024 - Present) Software Engineering

Professional Drawing Academy Foundation | Cali (2015 - 2018)

Graphic Designer

University of Las Palmas de Gran Canaria | Spain (2012 - 2015: Not completed)

Computer Engineering

CIFP Villa de Agüimes | Spain (2010 - 2012)

Superior Degree in Computer Applications Development

| Online Certifications

- Dart: From zero to Expert | (Devtalles)
- Vuejs: From zero to Expert | (Devtalles)
- Vuejs: Intermediate | (Devtalles)
- Typescript | (Udemy)

| Languages

Spanish (Native) English (B1)



